<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout android:orientation="vertical" android:background="@color/white" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="fill_parent"
  xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android">
    <RelativeLayout android:orientation="horizontal" android:id="@id/topid" android:background="@drawable/index_topbar" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="@dimen/commoncontent_topmargin" />
    <ScrollView android:id="@id/scene_control_scroll" android:scrollbars="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="fill_parent" android:layout_below="@id/topid">
        <RelativeLayout android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content">
            <TextView android:textSize="@dimen/dimen_size_s22" android:id="@id/title" android:layout_width="wrap_content" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/dimen_size_s10" android:text="Off control user agreement and privacy policy" android:layout_centerHorizontal="true" />
            <TextView android:ellipsize="none" android:scrollbars="vertical" android:layout_width="fill_parent" android:layout_height="wrap_content" android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/dimen_size_s20" android:text="This agreement is made between you and control information technology, Hangzhou concluded, this agreement is contractual effect. Hangzhou control guest information technology limited (following referred to control guest) agreed according to this agreement of provides and from time to time released of operation rules provides based on Internet, and real networking and mobile network of related service (following said network service), for get network service, service using people (following said user) should agreed this agreement of all terms and according to page Shang of tips completed all of registered program. Users in the registration process, click the agree button, which indicates that the user fully accepts all the terms of this agreement. \n 1. Service \n 1.1 control specific content for network services provided by the control according to the actual situation, such as data synchronization, electrical operations, share, comment, and so on. \n\n 1.2 user understanding and confirmed, control guest only provides related of network service, in addition of related network service about of equipment (as and control guest network service related of PC, and phone, and and he and access Internet or mobile network about of device) and the by needed of costs (as for access Internet and paid of phone fee and the Internet fee, and for using mobile network and paid of phone fee) are should by user itself bear. \n 1.3 user understands and recognizes that points earned by the user in control networks, users virtual currency, you can only control the allowable range, not available for transfer, sale and other purposes. \n 2. Use \n 2.1 user in applications using managed network services, you must provide accurate personal information to control, such as any change in the personal data, must be updated in a timely manner. \n 2.2 users should not be the account number, password, transfer or lend it to others. Users whose accounts were other illegal use, shall immediately notify the accused. Due to hacking or user negligence of custody accounts, passwords were illegally used, control does not assume any responsibility. \n 2.3 users understand and agree that controlling right in providing Internet service in a variety of ways put in all kinds of commercial advertising or any other type of business information (including, but not limited to advertising control on any page of the site), and you agree to be controlled via email or other means to send you product promotions or other business-related information. \n 2.4 for user through control guest network service Shang to control guest website Shang can public gets regional of any content, you agreed control guest in world range within has free of, and permanent of, and not revoked of, and non-exclusive of and completely again license of right and license, to using, and copy, and modified, and adapted, and published, and translation, and according to to creation derivative works, and spread, and performances and show this, content (overall or part), and/or will this, content into current known of or yihou development of other any form of works, and In the media or technology. \n 2.5 users in the use of process control network services, must adhere to the following principles: \n 2.5.1 compliance with relevant laws and regulations of China; \n 2.5.2 complying with all related to network services and network protocols, regulations and procedures; \n 2.5.3 shall not be used for any illegal purpose network service systems; \n 2.5.4 shall not to any form using control guest network service violations control guest of commercial interests, including does not limited to released non-by control guest license of commercial advertising; \n 2.5.5 shall not using control guest network service system for any may on Internet or mobile network normal running caused adverse effect of behavior; \n 2.5.6 shall not using control guest provides of network service upload, and show or spread any false of, and harassment sex of, and injured others of, and insults sex of, and intimidation sex of, and vulgar obscene of or other any illegal of information information; \n 2.5.7 shall not infringe any third party's patent, copyright, trademark, defamation or any other lawful rights and interests; \n 2.5.8 should not be used to control any network service system to control the behavior of guests. \n 2.6 control guest right to on you using control guest network service of situation for review and supervision (including but not limited to on you storage in control guest website of content for audit), as you in using network service Shi violation any above provides, control guest or its authorized of people right to requirements you corrected or directly take all necessary of measures (including but not limited to change or delete you posted of content,, and suspended or terminated you using network service of right) to reduce you of improper behavior caused of effect. \n 2.7 control for certain types of managed network services using a variety of methods (including but not limited to, Web announcements, e-mail, text message reminders, etc) of any declarations, notifications, alerts and other information as part of this agreement, the user uses the control network services, as users agree to the content of such declarations, notifications, alerts. \n 2.8 users agree to protect and maintain control and other user's interests, because if the user violates the relevant laws and regulations or any provision of this agreement to the Prosecutor or any other third party damages, user agrees to bear liability for the damage caused. \n 3. intellectual property \n 3.1 control guest provides of network service in the contains of any text, and pictures, and graphics, and audio and/or video information are by copyright, and trademark and/or other property ownership legal of protection, without related right people agreed, above information are shall not in any media directly or indirect released, and play, and for play or released purpose and rewrite or again issued, or was for other any commercial purpose. All such data and information may only be used as any part of personal and non-commercial use and stored in a computer. Controlled not by such information or in the transmission or transmitted in whole or in part of the above-mentioned information during delays, inaccuracies, errors or omissions or from which or any resulting damages, in any form, to the user or to any third party. \n 3.2 control guest for provides network service and using of any software (including but not limited to control guest synchronization software, and phone software and the software in the contains of pictures, and photos, and animation, and video, and recording, and music, and text and additional program, and with attached of help material) of all right are belongs to the software of copyright people, without the software of copyright people license, user shall not on the software for reverse engineering (reverse engineer), and Decompile (decompile) or disassembly (disassemble). \n\n 4. \n 4 privacy protection.1 protection user privacy is control guest of a items basic policy, control guest guarantee not foreign public or to third party provides single user of registered information and the user in using network service Shi storage in control guest of non-public content, but following situation except: \n 4.1.1 prior get user of clear authorized; \n 4.1.2 according to about of legal regulations requirements; \n 4.1.3 according to related government competent sector of requirements; \n 4.1.4 for maintenance social public of interests; \n 4.1.5 To maintain control of the legitimate rights and interests. \n 4.2 control may cooperate with third parties to provide users with relevant network service, in this case, if the third party agree to take equal responsibility to protect user privacy with controlled, user registration information, such as the accused is entitled to be provided to the third party. \n 4.3 does not disclose individual user privacy information under control right to the entire user database for analysis and commercial use of the user database. \n 5. Disclaimer \n 5.1 users expressly agree that the use network service the risk will be borne entirely by its own; by its use of managed network services and all the consequences arising from its own, control does not assume any responsibility to the user. \n 5.2 control does not guarantee network service will meet user's requirements, and does not guarantee the service will be uninterrupted, on network services timeliness, safety, accuracy is not guaranteed. \n 5.3 control does not guarantee that external links are set up for convenience to the user of accuracy and completeness, and the external links do not actually controlled by the control of any of the content on a Web page, control does not assume any responsibility. \n 5.4 due to force majeure or control network service interruptions caused by reasons beyond their control or other defects, control does not assume any responsibility, but will make every effort to reduce the damage caused to the user as a result and impact. \n 5.5 user agreed, for control guest to user provides of following products or service of quality defects itself and raised of any loss, control guest without bear any responsibility: \n 5.5.1 control guest to user free provides of the network service; \n 5.5.2 control guest to user gift of any products or service; \n 5.5.3 control guest to charges network service user attached gift of various products or service. \n 6. Agreement modifying \n 6.1 control has the right to modify any of the terms of this agreement at any time, once the content of the agreement changed, control directly in the control changes the contents of the agreement posted on the site, announced the acts considered controlled have informed users to modify content. Control can also be prompted to change the content to the user in an appropriate manner. \n 6.2 If you do not agree to control changes made to the relevant provisions of this agreement, users have the right to stop using Web services. If users continue to use network service, you as a user accept control modifications made to the relevant provisions of this agreement. \n 7. Service change, interrupt or terminate \n 7.1 given the particularity of the network services, user agrees to control the right to at any time change, interrupt or terminate part or all of the network services. Modification, interruption or termination of the network services are free Internet service, charged without notice to the user and without any liability to any user or to any third party such modification, interruption or termination charges of network service network service control should notify users in advance prior to the alteration, suspension or termination. \n 7.2 user understands and recognizes that control requires regular or ad hoc basis to provide network services platform (such as Internet, mobile, etc) or related equipment for repair or maintenance, control do not assume any responsibility, but the control should be given prior notice as possible. \n 7.3 as occurred following any a case, control guest right to at any time interrupted or terminated to user provides this agreement items Xia of network service (the network service including but not limited to charges and the free network service, and and based on advertising mode of free network service) and without on user or any third party bear any responsibility: \n 7.3.1 user provides of personal information not real; \n 7.3.2 user violation this agreement in the provides of using rules; \n 7.4 User registration control of customer network account nicknames such as violation of laws and regulations or national policy requirements, or violations of the legal rights of any third party, control the right to re-enter the account nickname. \n 8. Notice \n 8.1 controlled under this agreement for all of the user's notification can be via a Web page announcements, email, mobile APP, or regular mail delivery; the date of such notice in the paper deemed to have been delivered to the recipient. \n 8.2 users for control notification shall be controlled foreign official mailing address, e-mail address and other contact information for delivery. \n 9. Applicable law, jurisdiction and other \n 9.1 this agreement is entered into, executed and interpreted and settlement of disputes shall apply to Chinese law and subject to the jurisdiction of the County Court. \n 9.2 if any disputes arising in connection with this agreement or its implementation, the Parties shall try to amicably; negotiation fails, any party may initiate litigation to the people's Court, where the control. \n 9.3 this agreement constitutes the parties to this agreement agree matters and other matters relating to the entire agreement, apart from the provisions of this agreement, does not grant other rights of the parties to this agreement. \n 9.4 if any provision of this agreement, for any reason wholly or partly invalid or not enforceable, the remaining provisions of this Agreement shall remain valid and binding. \n 9.5 set headings in this agreement are for convenience only, and should be ignored in interpreting this agreement." android:maxLines="300" android:scrollHorizontally="false" android:singleLine="false" android:layout_below="@id/title" />\r\n
</RelativeLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>